TINEKE NASEEF

USER EXPERIENCE DESIGNER | SHE/HER

Westminster, CO 80031 | telnaseef@gmail.com | 720-203-6631

LinkedIn - https://bit.lv/3fCTHis | Portfolio - https://bit.lv/2ZOMIEb

SUMMARY

Highly adaptable and resourceful designer, combining creative problem solving and analytical skills with an attention to detail to create intuitive, accessible, usable solutions. Organized, highly-motivated hard-worker, equipped to work well in teams, but also independently. Background in customer service, social media, and communication; as well as expertise in Dutch and German, making for a highly versatile UX designer and researcher.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

UX/UI: Ideation, Interactive Design, Prototyping, Public Speaking/Presentation, Responsive Design, User Interviews, User Research, User Testing, Visual Design, Wireframing

DESIGN: Editing, Photo Editing, Photography, Social Media, Songwriting, Voiceover, Web Design, Writing **SOFTWARE**: Adobe Illustrator, Adobe Photoshop, Adobe Xd, Bootstrap, Figma, GitHub, Google Analytics, Google Drive, InVision, Jira, Microsoft Office Suite, Miro, Sketch, Trello

LANGUAGES: CSS, C++, HTML, JavaScript, jQuery

PROJECTS

pReTravel - https://tnaseef.github.io/UX Portfolio/pretravel.html

An app for researching experiences and vistas at travel destinations, in a low-pressure setting.

- User Experience and User Interface Designer
- Adobe Photoshop, Adobe Xd, Figma, FlowMapp, Google Drive, InVision, Uxpressia.com

GeekMeet - https://tnaseef.github.io/UX Portfolio/geekmeet.html

A community and interest-sharing app specifically designed for self-identifying "geeks" and "nerds."

- User Experience and User Interface Designer
- Figma, Google Drive, Google Forms, InVision, Miro, Whimsical

EXPERIENCE

Juniper Village - Spearly Center

Front Desk Receptionist

- Supervised up to 10 guests and patients at a time
- Enforced compliance with COVID-19 regulations
- Processed 10-50 faxes per day
- Helped improve experience for guests, patients and employees

American DataBank

Compliance and Immunization Team Member

- Reviewed approximately 700-800 documents per day
- Exceeded quota on over 90% of shifts
- Provided feedback and ideas to streamline review process
- Wrote copy for standardized document rejection notes

March 2021 - May 2021

Denver, CO

Nov 2019 - Sep 2020

Denver, CO

American DataBank

Applicant Success Team Member

Assisted users and clients through phone, ticket, and email channels

- Interacted with 100-200 users and clients per day
- Found innovative and resourceful solutions to user issues
- Organized project designing an FAQ page
- Processed around 100 background checks and/or document reviews per week
- Wrote copy for standardized responses to emails and chats

Layer3 TV / T-Mobile

Concierge Specialist, Social Media

- Assisted users through Twitter and Facebook
- Helped train a team of approximately 20 representatives
- Processed around 50 social media queries per shift
- Tested and monitored streaming services

Laver3 TV / T-Mobile

Layer3 Customer Care Concierge

- Provided exceptional customer service through phone, email and tickets
- Helped 30-50 users and processed around 20 tickets per shift
- Served as primary liaison with engineering team
- Tested and monitored streaming services
- Wrote copy for standardized responses to tickets, emails, and chats

PetSmart

Pet Care Specialist

- Single-handedly cleaned and cared for 8 bird cages, 12 rodent habitats, 30 fish tanks and 8 reptile terrariums
- Assisted approximately 10-20 customers daily with purchases and navigation
- Aided in stocking shelves and labeling merchandise
- Maintained up-to-date knowledge on approximately 15 species of pets
- Sold small pets and assisted with cat adoptions

University of Denver Call Center

Student Caller

- Called outbound to approximately 400 potential donors per shift
- Broke multiple team records, such as weekly donor numbers, donation amounts and credit card commits
- Helped train new employees
- Provided suggestions to improve systems and processes

EDUCATION

Certificate in UX/UI, University of Denver

Associate of General Studies Degree, Front Range Community College

Jan 2019 - Nov 2019

Denver, CO

July 2018 - Oct 2018

Denver, CO

May 2017 - July 2018

Denver, CO

June 2017 - August 2017

Westminster, CO

Feb 2016 – June 2016

Denver, CO

September 2021 May 2021